gxmarkets.com 2015-09-12

# Privacy Policy

Registered Office, 20-22, Wenlock, London, England, N 7GU

In today's world of identity theft and hacking, securing the private information of our customers is our top priority. The Privacy Policy below explains not only how we collect and protect your personal information, but also what our commitment is to you our customer. By opening an account with us or by using our website, you give your consent to allow us to collect and use your personal information in a reasonable manner. 

Your personal information is collected both directly from you and indirectly based on your relationship with our company. We may use this information for a variety of purposes including verifying your identity, issuing a secure password, maintaining your account activity and other reasons. We also use this information to help us improve our services to you, allowing us to customize your browsing and inform you of additional products and services.

Most of the information is what you provide to us directly, such as name, phone number, e-mail address, social security number and other relevant information. This information is given to us when you complete your account application, submit an e-mail or respond to a special offer or promotion. Information collected indirectly can include internet service provider, internet protocol address, and transaction history and time stamps.

We use cookies and other technology to provide us with data we can use to know you better. This technology allows us to determine when you arrive at or leave our site, what pages you view and when you are logged in to our site. We never share this information with third-party companies or individuals; it is only readable by us and does not contain account or password information. 

We employ many safeguards to protect your personal information including physical and electronic means. Only employees who have a direct need for your information will have access to it, and we recommend you do not disclose your account number and password to anyone. We use encryption technology such as VeriSign for added safety of your information, and we conduct regular audits of our system to ensure our confidentiality standards are meeting expectations.

We never disclose any private or otherwise confidential information in regards to our clients and former clients to third parties.

If any changes are made to this Privacy Policy, they will be posted to our site immediately. If at any time you wish to opt out of your account, you can do so by contacting us. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you may contact a Client Services Representative.
